A Guide to the Papers of Henry Evans Howell, Jr. 1948-1976
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University Libraries, Old Dominion University
- Political Papers 1948-1973
  - Sub-Series F: 1963 General Assembly Campaign
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign: Pre-Primary Correspondence, December 1962- March 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 12)
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign: Pre-Primary Correspondence, April- July, 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 13)
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign: Post Primary Correspondence, July-August, 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Sub -Series G: 1964-1967
    - General Correspondence, January-June, 1964 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, July-December, 1964 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 2)
    - 1964 Presidential Election in Virginia, July-November, 1964 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, January-June, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, July-December, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence among Anti-Byrd Democrats, April-December, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Howell Involvement in 1965 Democratic Primaries, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 7)
    - 1965 General Assembly Campaign: "Norfolk First", Campaign Materials, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 8)
    - 1965 General Assembly Campaign: "Norfolk First", Campaign Materials, Norfolk First, Berry Willis, Administration Slate, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 9)
    - 1965 General Assembly Campaign: "Norfolk First", General Correspondence, February-August, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 10)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Campaign Materials, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 11)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Finances, Bank Account Records, April-August, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 12)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Finances, Expenditures - Correspondence, Invoices, March-November, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 13)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Finances, Fundraising (Correspondence among Fundraisers), April-September, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 14)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Finances, Fundraising (Letters Seeking Contributions), May-June, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 15)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Finances, Fundraising (Correspondence with Contributors), May-July, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 16)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Finances, Fundraising (Miscellaneous Records of Contributions), 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 17)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Lists of Campaign Workers, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 18)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Mailing Lists, Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 19)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Miscellaneous Materials, 1965 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 1)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Pre-Primary Correspondence, November 1964-March 1965 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 2)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Pre-Primary Correspondence, April- May, 1965 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 3)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Pre-Primary Correspondence, June 1965 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 4)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Pre-Primary Correspondence, July 1965 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 5)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Correspondence re: Reapportionment Victory Banquet (June 29, 1965), May-July, 1965 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 6)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Correspondence re: Howell Primary Win, July-August, 1965 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 7)
    - 1965 State Senate Campaign: Correspondence re: November Election, September-November, 1965 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Howell for U.S. Senate Boomlet (1965-1966): Plans, Polls, Campaign Materials (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Howell for U.S. Senate Boomlet (1965-1966): Campaign Materials (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Howell for U.S. Senate Boomlet (1965-1966): Miscellaneous Lists of Virginia Democrats (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Howell for U.S. Senate Boomlet (1965-1966): Miscellaneous Materials (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Howell for U.S. Senate Boomlet (1965-1966), General Correspondence, October 1965 - March 1966 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Anti-Byrd Democrats: General Correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Armistead L. Boothe Senatorial Campaign: Tidewater Effort, March-August, 1966 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 16)
    - William B. Spong U.S. Senatorial Campaign: Joe Fitzpatrick Correspondence, General Correspondence, March-August, 1966 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 17)
    - 1966 Virginia Elections: Democratic Primary, General Election, March-October, 1966 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, January-March, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, April-December, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 3)
    - 1967 General Assembly Campaign-"Norfolk First": Correspondence, Campaign Materials, March-October, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 4)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Finances, Bank Account Records, May-December, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 5)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Finances, Expenditures, Correspondence, Invoices, June-November, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 6)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Finances, Fundraising, Letters Soliciting Contributions, May 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 7)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Finances, Fundraising, Correspondence with Contributors, May-July, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 8)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Finances, Fundraising, Miscellaneous Records, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 9)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Miscellaneous Materials, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 10)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Pre-Primary Correspondence, January-March, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 11)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Pre-Primary Correspondence, April-May, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 12)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Pre-Primary Correspondence, June-July, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 13)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Correspondence re: Howell Primary Victory, July-August, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 14)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Correspondence re: November General Election, July-August, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 15)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Correspondence re: November General Election, September-November, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 16)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign: Post-Election Correspondence, November-December, 1967 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 17)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign (Breeden - Howell - Roberts Ticket): General Correspondence, March-June, 1967 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 1)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign (Breeden - Howell - Roberts Ticket): General Correspondence, July-October, 1967 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 2)
    - 1967 State Senate Campaign (Breeden - Howell - Roberts Ticket): Campaign Materials, Literature (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series H: General & Correspondence with Other Politicians
    - General Correspondence (Prior to Beginning of Howell for Governor Campaign), January-March, 1968 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence (Prior to Beginning of Howell for Governor Campaign), April-June, 1968 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 5)
    - "Bingo" Stant Congressional Campaign: 2nd District, Miscellaneous Material re: Democratic Primary, 1968 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 6)
    - "Bingo" Stant Congressional Campaign: 2nd District, Campaign Materials, Stant, John Rixey, 1968 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 7)
    - "Bingo" Stant Congressional Campaign: 2nd District, Correspondence re: Democratic Primary, March-June 1968 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 8)
    - "Bingo" Stant Congressional Campaign: 2nd District, Miscellaneous Materials re: November Election (G. William Whitehurst, Republican Opponent), November 1968 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Watkins M. Abbitt - Howell Correspondence (Democratic Congressmanand State Democratic Chairman), 1967 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 10)
    - George E. Allen, Jr. (Anti-Byrd Democrat, No. Va.)-Howell Correspondence, 1962-1967 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 11)
    - J. Lindsay Almond, Jr. - Howell Correspondence (Governorship), 1959-1961 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 12)
    - William C. Battle - Howell Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Armistead L. Boothe - Howell Correspondence, 1960-1968 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Robert Y. Button (Attorney-General of Virginia) - Howell Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Harry F. Byrd, Jr. - Howell Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Rev. John Paul (Jack) Carter (Episcopal Priest, Anti- Byrd Democrat) -Howell Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Mills Godwin - Howell Correspondence (Lt. Governorship), 1964-1965 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Mills Godwin - Howell Correspondence (Governorship), 1966 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Mills Godwin - Howell Correspondence (Governorship), January 1967- May 1968 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Dr. Edward E. Haddock (Anti-Byrd Democrat, Richmond) - Howell Correspondence, 1956-1965 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Albertis S. Harrison, Jr. - Howell Correspondence, 1961-1965 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 2)
    - W. Pat Jennings - Howell Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Augustus C. ("Gus") Johnson (Anti-Byrd Democrat, No. Va.) - Howell Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 4)
    - C. Harrison Mann (Delegate, No. Va.) - Howell Correspondence, 1959-1965 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Francis Pickens Miller - Howell Correspondence, 1952-1959 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Francis Pickens Miller - Howell Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 7)
    - H. Graham Morrison (Anti-Byrd Democrat, No. Va.) - Howell Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Fred J. Pollard - Howell Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 9)
    - George C. Rawlings, Jr. - Howell Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 10)
    - J. Sargeant Reynolds - Howell Correspondence, 1962 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Richard S. (Major) Reynolds - Howell Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 12)
    - A. Willis Robertson - Howell Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 13)
    - William B. Spong, Jr. - Howell Correspondence, 1960-1968 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 14)
    - A.E.S. ("Gi") Stephens - Howell Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Robert Whitehead (Older Anti-Byrd Democrat) - Howell Correspondence, 1952-1959 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Murat Williams (Liberal Democrat, No. Va.) - Howell Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Peter Babalas -Howell Correspondence, 1959-1968 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Robert F. Baldwin - Howell Correspondence, 1959-1968 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Edward L. Breeden, Jr. - Howell Correspondence, 1952-1968 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Joseph T. Fitzpatrick - Howell Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Arthur T. Freeman (Key Black Supporter) - Howell Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Hon. Porter Hardy, Jr. - Howell Correspondence, 1949-1964 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Hon. Porter Hardy, Jr. - Howell Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 2)
    - H. Lee Kanter (Key Howell Supporter in Norfolk) - Howell Correspondence, 1954-1968 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Col. James W. Roberts (State Legislator from Norfolk) - Howell Correspondence, 1959-1967 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Stanley E. Sacks - Howell Correspondence, 1959-1968 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Frederick T. ("Bingo") Stant, Jr. - Howell Correspondence, 1959-1968 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence with Norfolk Delegation to General Assembly, 1959-1967 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence with Individual Members of Norfolk Delegation: Delamater Davis, Bernard Levin, Thomas McNamara, Thomas Moss, Theodore Pilcher, Toy Savage, John Sears, Stanley Walker, J. Warren White (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 8)
    - City of Norfolk - Correspondence with Mayors: Fred Duckworth (1960), Roy B. Martin, Jr. (1963-1968), 1960-1968 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 9)
    - City of Norfolk - Correspondence with City Manager Thomas Maxwell, 1960-1968 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 10)
    - City of Norfolk - Correspondence with Clerk of Courts William L.Prieur, Jr., 1960-1963 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 11)
    - City of Norfolk - Police Department: Correspondence with Claude J. Staylor, 1959-1967 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 12)
    - City of Norfolk -Correspondence with City Attorney's Office: Leonard Davis (C.A.), S.W. McCann, Jr. (Asst. C.A.), 1960-1967 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 13)
    - City of Norfolk - Correspondence with Miscellaneous City Officials, 1960-1968 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series I: Correspondence with Labor Leaders
    - Labor: Paul Askew -Howell Correspondence, 1954-1968 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Labor: Wilbur Hobby - Howell Correspondence (Regional COPE Director), 1959-1966 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Labor: Murray Pierce (Int. Union of Operating Engineers, Norfolk COPE), 1959-1966 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Labor: Vivian Stringfield (Brotherhood of Railway Engineers) - Howell Correspondence, 1959-1968 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Labor: David Alston (ILA) -Howell Correspondence, 1961-1967 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Labor: Hampton Roads Port Council - Howell Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Labor: Railway Clerks and Trainmen - Howell Correspondence, 1959-1968 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Labor: U.A.W. - Howell Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Labor: Miscellaneous Correspondence with Union Officials, 1952-1968 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Labor: Norfolk COPE (AFL-CIO), A.L. "Pappy" Redfearn, 1959-1967 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Labor: National COPE - Howell Correspondence, 1959-1966 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Labor: Correspondence with Va. AFL-CIO Headquarters (Harold B. Boyd, Pres.), 1959-1966 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Labor: Correspondence with Ca. AFL-CIO (Julian Carper, V.P.), 1960-1966 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Labor: Correspondence with Va. AFL-CIO Headquarters (Julian Carper, Pres.), 1966-1968 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Labor: Correspondence with Va. AFL-CIO Headquarters (Brewster Snow, Sect. Treasurer), 1959-1967 Sub-Series J: 1969 Gubernatorial Campaign (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 9)
    - HEH General Correspondence, July-December, 1967 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 10)
    - HEH General Correspondence, January-April, 1968 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 11)
    - HEH General Correspondence, May-December, 1968 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 12)
    - HEH General Correspondence, January-July, 1969 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 13)
    - HEH Post Runoff Primary Correspondence, August-October, 1969 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Announcement of Candidacy, Public Responses, Howell Replies, June-July, 1968 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Announcement of Candidacy, Correspondence with Legislators (Past and Present), June-July, 1968 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence re: Humphrey- Muskie Ticket, August-November, 1968 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Official Declaration of Candidacy, Request for Runoff, April- July, 1969 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 18)
    - William C. Battle - Howell Correspondence (Post-Primary), August-September, 1969 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Governor Mills Godwin - Howell Correspondence, April 1968 -August 1969 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 20)
    - George Grayson - Howell Correspondence, September 1968 - May 1969 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Va. Young Democrats - Howell Correspondence, May 1968 - July 1969 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 22)
  - 1969 Gubernatorial Campaign 1969
    - HEH Correspondence with Active Supporters, First Primary, February-September, 1968 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 1)
    - HEH Correspondence with Active Supporters, First Primary, October-December, 1968 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 2)
    - HEH Correspondence with Active Supporters, First Primary, January-March, 1969 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 3)
    - HEH Correspondence with Active Supporters, First Primary, April-July, 1969 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 4)
    - HEH Correspondence with Active Supporters, Runoff, July-August, 1969 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Letters from Voters, First Primary, August-December, 1968 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Letters from Voters, First Primary, January-March, 1969 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Letters from Voters, First Primary, April-July, 1969 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Letters from Voters during Runoff, July-August, 1969 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Letters from Voters with Howell Responses, January- August, 1969 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Letters to HEH Unanswered During Campaign (Assigned to Jim Burch), June-August, 1969 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 1)
    - "Crank" Letters or Letters Critical of Howell, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Letters from Former Supporters Now Backing Battle, February- March, 1969 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Form Letters (Howell Signature), 1968 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Form Letters (Howell Signature), 1969 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Rough Drafts for Form Letters, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Form Letters for No. Va., Correspondence (Rough Drafts), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Betty Howell Correspondence and Press Releases, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Staff Correspondence, Dick Bayer, 1969 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Staff Correspondence, Bob Brown, 1968 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Staff Correspondence, Bob Brown, 1969 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder11)
    - Staff Correspondence, Bob Brown ("Bingo" Stant Congressional Campaign), April-November, 1968 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Staff Correspondence, Bob Brown (Humphrey-Muskie Campaign), April-November, 1968 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Staff Correspondence, Bob Brown (Howell Christmas Cards), November-December, 1968 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Staff Correspondence, Bob Brown -George Grayson Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Bob Brown - George Grayson (Va. Vote-Flow Survey), October- December, 1968 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Staff Correspondence, Bob Brown - George Grayson (Study of 1969 Campaign), October-December, 1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Staff Correspondence, Bob Brown - Virginia Council on Human Relations, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Staff Correspondence, Bob Brown (Personal), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Staff Correspondence, Jim Burch (General), August 1968-March 1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Staff Correspondence, Jim Burch (General), April-June, 1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Staff Correspondence, Jim Burch - George Grayson (Speeches, Issues) 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Staff Correspondence, Gary Estes, 1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Staff Correspondence, Elyce Fishman, April-July, 1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Staff Correspondence, Joe Fitzpatrick (General), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Staff Correspondence, Joe Fitzpatrick (1968 Democratic Convention), August 1968 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Staff Correspondence, Communications with George Rawlings, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Staff Correspondence, Communication with Rev. Jack Carter, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Staff Correspondence, Inquiries re:Hatch Act, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Staff Correspondence, Communications with Va. Young Democrats, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Staff Correspondence, Form Letters (Final Versions, Rough Drafts), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Intra-Staff, Henry Howell - Bob Brown, Memos, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Intra-Staff, Henry Howell - Jim Eurch Memos, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Intra-Staff, Henry Howell -Joe Fitzpatrick Memos, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Intra-Staff, Misc. Memos to Henry Howell, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Intra-Staff, Bob Brown -Jim Burch Memos, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Intra-Staff, Bob Brown -Catharine Crane Memos, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Intra-Staff, Bob Brown -Gary Estes Memos, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Intra-Staff, Bob Brown -Don Green, January-June, 1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Intra-Staff, Bob Brown -Jane Vitray, 1969 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Intra-Staff, Misc. Memos from Bob Brown, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Intra-Staff, Misc. Memos to Bob Brown, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Intra-Staff, Jim Burch - Jean Howell re: Volunteers, 1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Intra-Staff, Jim Burch, Memos from, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Intra-Staff, Dorothy Disharoon, Memos to, 1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Intra-Staff, Joe Fitzpatrick - Bob Brown Memos, 1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Intra-Staff, Joe Fitzpatrick -Jim Burch Memos, 1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Intra-Staff, Joe Fitzpatrick, Memos from and to, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Intra-Staff, Arthur T. Freeman, Memos to and from, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Intra-Staff, Ben Ragsdale, Memos to and from, 1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Intra-Staff, General Memos, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Staff Notes, Sheets from Note Pads, 1968 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Staff Notes, Sheets from Note Pads, 1968 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Staff Notes, Sheets from Notebooks, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Staff Notes, Sheets from Notebooks (undated), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Staff Notes, Sheets from Notebooks, 1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Staff Notes, Sheets from Note Pads, 1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Staff Notes - Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Black Vote, "Get Out the Vote" Drive (Arthur Freeman), First Primary, October 1968 - July 1969 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Black Vote, "Get Out the Vote" Drive (Arthur Freeman), Runoff, July-August, 1969 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Black Vote, Misc. Mailing Lists, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Black Vote, Records of Key Howell Supporters, 1969 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Materials, Brochure - Campaign Communications Institute of America, 1969 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Materials, Brochures - Misc., 1969 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Materials, Commercial Catalogues, 1969 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Materials, Correspondence and Notes re: Printing Campaign Materials, 1969 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Materials, Buttons - Correspondence, Drawings, 1969 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Materials, Designs by Richmond Professional Institute, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Materials, Drafts of Literature, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Materials, Dresses for Howell Girls, 1968 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 12)